superkids.com 2019-06-23

# SuperKids Privacy Policy.

**software**  
  reviews   
  bestseller list   
  price survey   
  what's new   
  product support   
  search **educational tools**   
  math worksheets   
  vocabulary builders   
  hangman   
  checkers, etc. **feature articles** **marketplace**  
  reading corner  
  movie corner **SuperKids**  
  about SuperKids  
  advertise!   
  humor  
  links  
  help |  |  home > > > privacy policy  Our privacy policy is simple: SuperKids does not collect personal information from visitors to our site without their knowledge and consent. 

The only place where any individual user information is collected, is through optional participation in certain contests and sweepstakes. That information may be used to create aggregated demographic profiles of our visitors -- but it is never revealed on an individual basis to anyone outside of the SuperKids organization. Aggregated information like this allows us to better tailor our content to readers' needs and to help our advertisers better understand the demographics of our audience. Because SuperKids derives some of it's revenue from advertising, providing such aggregated demographic data is essential to keeping our service free to users. 

**Children's Privacy**   
Under the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, no web site operator is permitted to require a child under the age of 13 to disclose more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in an activity as a condition of participation. SuperKids abides by this requirement. 

**Cookies**   
A cookie is a small message that may be written to your hard drive by some Web servers. Your browser stores the message in a text file called cookie.txt. The message is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. The main purpose of cookies is to identify users and possibly prepare customized Web pages for them. Some users fear that the use of cookies may compromise their privacy. 

SuperKids does not use any cookies to track or identify visitors to our site. Cookies appear in only two places on SuperKids: 

  * Advertisers. Some advertisers on SuperKids use cookies to limit the number of times they show a particular ad banner to each computer. These cookies are associated with the ad banners only, and are never transmitted back to SuperKids. We use third-party advertising companies to serve some of the ads you see when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 
  * Several of the Logic Games on SuperKids' site use cookies to keep track of where a user is in a game. For example, in the Hangman Game for The United States, the page uses cookies to keep track of which games and letters have been played, to avoid premature repetition. No user information is transmitted back to SuperKids. 

**Surveys**   
SuperKids occasionally conducts user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with advertisers and partners. We never share any information about specific individuals with any third party. 

**Questions?**   
Please email us if you have any questions about our privacy policy, at: [Privacy Question](mailto:webmaster@superkids.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Question)

back to top of page

* * *

Questions or comments regarding this site? [webmaster@superkids.com](mailto:webmaster@superkids.com)   
Copyright © 1998-2007 Knowledge Share LLC. All rights reserved. Privacy Policy
